A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Snapshot Files, RG 4 FA1128C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Travel (500), 1924-1989; 6
  - 500,127 China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 5- Beijing, Forbidden City, Guest House park. (Negatives filed with CS 67-68.)
  - 500,128 China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 6- Foreign Policy Delegation, Guilin. (Negatives filed with CS 69-70.)
  - 500,129 China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 7- Bonzai trees, Guilin canals, guset house on lake, Commune villages. (Negatives filed with CS 71.)
  - 500,130 China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 8- Last day, Guilin. (Negatives filed with CS 72-73.)
  - 500,131 China, 1985 November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 10- Group at dinner with hot pot. Prints and disc negatives.
  - 500,132 China, 1985 November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 11- YWCA Shanghai, Arts and Craft Shop, MFR with Chinese women and children. Prints and disc negatives.
  - 500,133 China, 1985 November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 12- Shanghai, MFR with YWCA leader? Prints and disc negatives.
  - 500,134 China, 1985 November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 14- Guest houses, Jeep Plant, Beijing. Prints and disc negatives.
  - 500,135 China, 1985 November (Box 16)
    Envelope no. 15- China views, MFR. Prints and disc negatives.
  - 500,137 China, 1985 October - November (Box 16)
    China trip, Beijing, general.
  - 500,141 China- Hong Kong, 1985 November (Box 16)
    Hong Kong views; Thanksgiving lunch at 834 Fifth Ave.
  - 500,142 China- Hong Kong, 1985 October-November (Box 16)
    Mainly China - river trip, street views, children, etc. A few views of Hong Kong harbor.
  - 500,143 China- Hong Kong, 1985 November (Box 16)
    Buildings, harbor, artwork.
  - 500,144 Caribbean- Caneel Bay, Cinnamon Bay, Necker Island, Sea Star, 1986 January (Box 16)
  - 500,145 Vessels- Evening Star to Necker Island, 1986 January (Box 16)
  - 500,146 Vessels- Sea Star and Dauntless Models, 1988 February 23 (Box 16)
    Models on display at New York Yacht Club. Also includes artwork at Room 5600, 30 Rockefeller Center.
  - 500,146.1 Vessels- Caribbean, 1986 March (Box 16)
    Sailboats at anchor, sunset, rainbow.
  - 500,147 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
  - 500,148 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
  - 500,149 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
  - 500,150 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
  - 500,151 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
  - 500,152 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
    Yucatan, Mayan ruins.
  - 500,153 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
  - 500,154 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
    Yucatan, Mayan temple, Club Med
  - 500,155 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
    Yucatan, Mayan temple.
  - 500,156 Mexico, 1986 March (Box 17)
    Yucatan, Mayan ruins, Club Med hotel
  - 500,157 (1) Mexico, 1988 (Box 17)
    Unidentified modern buildings; ruins.
  - 500,157 (2) Mexico, 1988 (Box 17)
  - 500,158 (1) Russia, 1989 September (Box 17)
    LSR and MFR, visits and meetings.
  - 500,158 (2) Russia, 1989 September (Box 17)
    LSR, MFR, and unidentified group. Meetings and visits. Occasion not identified.
  - Separated Negatives (Box 25)
    Rolled negative strips separated from Series 500 snapshot files: from envelopes 500,011 (1 roll); 500,012 (3 rolls, numbered 421, 434, and 435); 500,013 (2 rolls, numbered 424 and 427); 500,014 (2 rolls, numbered 428 and 433); 500,015 (3 rolls, numbered 425, 431, and 436); 500,017 (2 rolls, numbered 422 and 467); and 500,018 (1 roll, numbered 423).
- Resorts (600), 1950-1990; 7
  - 600,000 Unidentified Construction, Late 1940s - 1950s (Box 17)
    Unidentified housing construction (foundations and finished houses). Black and white photos. (One roll of negatives stored separately in box 25.)
  - 600,000 Unidentified Construction (Negatives) (Box 25)
    One roll of black-and-white negatives. (Corresponding prints are stamped E153.) Negative roll separated from envelope 600,000.
  - 600,001 Arizona- Boulders, 1985 (Box 17)
  - 600,002 Arizona- Boulders, 1985 (Box 17)
  - 600,003 Arizona- Boulders, 1985 March (Box 17)
  - 600,004 Arizona- Boulders, 1985 March (Box 17)
  - 600,090.3 Little Dix Bay, 1978 February (Box 17)
  - 600,005 Arizona- Boulders, 1985 March (Box 17)
  - 600,006 Arizona- Boulders, 1985 March (Box 17)
  - 600,007 Caneel Bay, circa 1954 (Box 17)
    Fritz Henle photos.
  - 600,008 Dorado Beach, 1954-1963 (Box 17)
    Views, construction, golf tournaments.
  - 600,009 Sandy Cay, 1956; Undated (Box 17)
    View of Sandy Cay island; Dorado Beach
  - 600,010 Virgin Islands (General), 1950s-1971 (Box 17)
  - 600,010.1 Caneel Bay, 1952 (Box 17)
    Captioned prints of cottages and bays. Prints badly yellowed.
  - 600,011 Dorado Beach, 1954 April (Box 17)
    One print of beach.
  - 600,012 Dorado Beach, 1954 October (Box 17)
    Beach views. One print of MFR; one print of unidentified woman on horse (at JY Ranch).
  - 600,013 Peter Island (BVI), Caneel Bay, circa 1955? (Box 17)
    Fritz Henle photos; includes LSR and MFR.
  - 600,014 Dorado Beach, 1954 November (Box 17)
  - 600,015 Dorado Beach Golf Course, 1956 October (Box 17)
    Captioned images of golf course construction and beaches.
  - 600,016 Cabo Blanco, Peru, 1956 (Box 17)
    Fishing trip with Roger Firestone- MFR and LSR napping on boat.
  - 600,017 Cabo Blanco, Peru; Caneel Bay, 1956 March (Box 17)
    Fishing trip with Roger Firestone. MFR and LSR on fishing boat, marlins, local children on pier; Caneel Bay.
  - 600,017 Cabo Blanco, Peru; Caneel Bay, 1956 March (Box 17)
    Fishing trip with Roger Firestone. MFR and local children on pier. Caneel Bay and Virgin Islands.
  - 600,019 Cabo Blanco, Peru, 1956 March (Box 18)
    Fishing trip with Roger Firestone.
  - 600,020 Cabo Blanco, Peru, 1956 March (Box 18)
    MFR and others on boat.
  - 600,021 Puerto Rico; Caneel Bay, 1956 (Box 18)
    Luis Munoz Marin at construction site; drainage construction at Caneel; Dauntless.
  - 600,022 St. Thomas, 1956 April (Box 18)
    Two images of Babs, Jean Mauze, NAR, and Mary Tod Rockefeller.
  - 600,023 Caneel Bay, 1956 April (Box 18)
    Dock.
  - 600,024 Sandy Cay, 1956 April (Box 18)
    MFR, Alston Boyer, NAR, and others.
  - 600,025 Caneel Bay, 1956 April (Box 18)
  - 600,026 Virgin Islands, 1956; 1967 (Box 18)
  - 600,027 Caneel Bay, 1956 April (Box 18)
    Construction, views, LSR family.
  - 600,028 Caneel Bay, 1956 May (Box 18)
  - 600,029 Dorado Beach, 1956 October (Box 18)
    Includes a few images from Caneel Bay.
  - 600,030 Caribbean, 1956 October (Box 18)
  - 600,031 Caneel Bay, 1956 December (Box 18)
  - 600,032 San Juan, PR, 1956 December (Box 18)
    Aerial views; grocery store under construction; other construction.
  - 600,033 Caribbean, 1956 (Box 18)
    Caneel Bay; IBEC construction site.
  - 600,034 Virgin Islands; Dorado Beach, 1957 (Box 18)
  - 600,035 Caneel Bay, 1957 February (Box 18)
  - 600,036 Caneel Bay; Dorado Beach, 1957 March (Box 18)
  - 600,037 Caribbean, 1957 March (Box 18)
    Dorado Beach and golf course; Caneel Bay; MFR, NAR, Boyer, and unidentified couple dining.
  - 600,038 Caneel Bay, Virgin Islands, 1957 March (Box 18)
    Virgin Islands views, dock, construction; Caneel Bay, NAR, and others.
  - 600,039 Virgin Islands, 1957 March (Box 18)
    Views; includes image from Dorado
  - 600,040 Dorado Beach, 1957 April (Box 18)
    Aerial views, golf; also Virgin Islands views.
  - 600,041 Dorado Beach, Virgin Islands, 1957 April (Box 18)
    Caneel Bay and Dorado Beach.
  - 600,042 Dorado Beach, Puerto Rico, Caneel Bay, 1957 April (Box 18)
    Aerial views of Dorado and San Juan, fishermen; cattle; some views of Caneel Bay.
  - 600,043 Caneel Bay, 1957 April (Box 18)
    Views from the bay.
  - 600,044 Virgin Islands, 1957 April (Box 18)
  - 600,045 Kykuit - Playhouse Pool, 1957 August (Box 18)
    NAR at pool; two images of boating on Hudson River.
  - 600,046 Virgin Islands, 1957 August (Box 18)
    Wake of boat. One image.
  - 600,047 Vessels, 1957 October (Box 18)
    Dauntless, sailboat.
  - 600,048 Caribbean, 1957 October (Box 18)
    LSR and MFR. One image.
  - 600,049 Caneel Bay and Dorado Beach, 1958 January (Box 18)
    Aerial and beach views, views from bay, golf course.
  - 600,050 Dorado Beach, 1958 January (Box 18)
    Construction, LSR family playing golf.
  - 600,051 Caribbean, 1958 January (Box 18)
    LSR family, DR and Peggy Rockefeller, sailing; location unidentified.
  - 600,052 Caribbean, Dorado Beach, 1958 February (Box 18)
    LSR family, DR and Peggy Rockefeller, sailing; includes views of Dorado Beach.
  - 600,053 Caribbean- Vessels, 1958 February (Box 18)
    Unidentified sailing yacht.
  - 600,054 Caneel Bay, 1958 March (Box 18)
    Construction; donkeys; cacti.
  - 600,055 Caneel Bay, 1958 March (Box 18)
    Unidentified house above shore and residents; cacti.
  - 600,056 Caneel Bay, 1958 April (Box 18)
    Construction, grounds, views; Mauretania oceanliner; Lucy R. and friend; LSR family and friends.
  - 600,057 Caneel Bay (Views), 1958 April (Box 18)
    General landscape and water views; MFR, family and friends.
  - 600,058 Virgin Island Views, Caneel Bay, 1958 April (Box 18)
    Includes MFR, family and friends; Eddie and Adelaide Rickenbacker.
  - 600,059 Dauntless, 1958 September (Box 18)
    MFR and children on dock.
  - 600,060 Caneel Bay, 1958 September (Box 18)
    View.
  - 600,061 Caribbean, 1958 October (Box 18)
    Unidentified view of water and shore.
  - 600,062 Dorado Beach, 1958 October (Box 18)
    Views and buildings. Also includes LSR, MFR, DR, Peggy R., and Happy R. boating.
  - 600,063 Dorado Beach, 1958 December (Box 18)
  - 600,064 Virgin Islands, Caneel Bay, 1959 January (Box 19)
    MFR with unidentified guests, Sandy Cay. Includes image of man with sketch pad.
  - 600,065 Dorado Beach, 1959 Febuary (Box 19)
    Pool and golf club. Unidentified guests.
  - 600,066 Virgin Islands, Caneel Bay, Dorado Beach, 1959 April (Box 19)
    Sailing, views, cattle, unidentified guests.
  - 600,067 Mexico- Acapulco, 1959 October (Box 19)
    MFR with marlin.
  - 600,068 Virgin Islands, 1968 June (Box 19)
  - 600,069 Hawaii, 1960 August (Box 19)
    Also views from airplane of mountains and snow (possibly Alaska).
  - 600,070 LSR and MFR, 1960 October (Box 19)
    MFR in fur parka with puppy; LSR and MFR on the Wayfarer, October 30, 1960.
  - 600,070.1 Hawaii, 1961 June (Box 19)
    LSR at airport,with with leis.
  - 600,071 Caribbean, 1961 November (Box 19)
    Sailboat, shore and bay views, woman at Caneel, unidentified place.
  - 600,072 Caribbean, 1962 April (Box 19)
    LSR with binoculars overlooking shore and on boat; view of marina (possibly Dorado?); LSR, MFR, and daughter.
  - 600,073 Dorado Beach, 1962 October (Box 19)
    LSR and MFR golfing.
  - 600,074 Caribbean, 1962 November (Box 19)
    Unidentified beach view.
  - 600,075 Caneel Bay, 1963 August (Box 19)
    Cottage 7 interior and patio views. (Scanned photos, UI- 813701, 813702, 813703. )
  - 600,076 Little Dix Bay; Mauna Kea, 1963-1965; 1971 (Box 19)
    LSR and MFR at Little Dix Bay, LDB beach views. LSR and MFR on Savanna Bay, at Little Dix, Mauna Kea Beach construction (golf course and hotel).
  - 600,077 Caribbean, 1964 March (Box 19)
    Sailboats.
  - 600,078 Mauna Kea Beach, 1964 July (Box 19)
  - 600,079 Hawaii?, 1964 August (Box 19)
    LSR with group of men and women overlooking shore; construction (possibly Mauna Kea).
  - 600,080 LSR with Ethan and Elizabeth Hitchcock and others, 1965 February (Box 19)
    On board sailing ship.
  - 600,081 Little Dix Bay, 1965 May (Box 19)
    Views of bay and resort, ships and sailboats.
  - 600,082 LSR at Caneel Bay, 1965 August (Box 19)
  - 600,082.1 Little Dix Bay, 1968 April (Box 19)
  - 600,082,2 Dorado Beach, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
    LSR and MFR and unidentified people; LSR at Dorado Beach golf course with Chi Chi Rodriguez
  - 600,083 Caneel Bay, 1968 November (Box 19)
    View of Hawk's Nest Beach. File includes letter and note from Mandie and Vietor Davis.
  - 600,083.1 Caribbean, 1969 March (Box 19)
    Unidentified location, possibly BVI. LSR with soldier, diver, other unidentified people.
  - 600,084 Virgin Islands, 1971 (Box 19)
    LSR, MFR, Elizabeth Hitchcock, and others on sailboat. Includes note from Elizabeth Hitchcock.
  - 600,085 Caribbean, 1971 April (Box 19)
    Elizabeth and Ethan Hitchcock swimming off ship.
  - 600,086 Virgin Islands, 1973 April (Box 19)
    LSR and MFR with unidentified people; sailing and crew.
  - 600,087 Virgin Islands; Sea Star, 1973 (Box 19)
    Views of boat at anchor and sailing; LSR onboard ship with unidentified people, April 1973. Slides, August 1973, of unidentified flooding, and sailing party.
  - 600,088 Hawaii, 1976 May (Box 19)
    Aerial view of golf course and shoreline - Mauna Kea?
  - 600,089 Little Dix Bay, 1978 February (Box 19)
    Prints and slides. Some images not included in albums.
  - 600,090 Little Dix Bay, 1978 February (Box 19)
    Scenic views, boats. Prints and slides. Some images not included in albums.
  - 600,090.1 Little Dix Bay, 1978 February (Box 19)
    Boats, views, unidentified man. Includes a few Caneel Bay photos.
  - 600,090.2 Little Dix Bay, Evening Star, 1978 February (Box 19)
    Includes MFR and others
  - 600,090.3 Little Dix Bay, 1978 February (Box 19)
  - 600,090.4 Little Dix Bay, 1978 February (Box 19)
    Views, political signs, MFR and others (including Carlisle Humelsine?).
  - 600,091 Little Dix Bay, St. John, 1978 February-July (Box 19)
    Beach and dock; sugar mill ruin
  - 600,092 Little Dix Bay, 1978 June (Box 19)
    Views; unidentified group of visitors.
  - 600,093 Virgin Islands, 1978 October - 1979 January (Box 19)
  - 600,094 Little Dix, Sandy Cay, Pocantico, 1980s (Box 19)
    Views; Sandy Cay vegetation and views; trees and Hudson River views
  - 600,095 Caneel Bay, circa 1980 (Box 19)
    Includes aerial view of Caneel Bay; MFR with arm in cast.
  - 600,096 Caneel Bay, circa 1980 (Box 19)
  - 600,097 Caneel Bay, 1980 (Box 19)
    "Views from Gus Starke's old house on hill." Also includes Bancel LaFarge and two other men on beach at Caneel.
  - 600,098 Little Dix Bay, circa 1980 (Box 19)
    MFR sailing; LSR, MFR, and unidentified friends; views.
  - 600,099 Little Dix Bay, 1980 (Box 19)
  - 600,100 Little Dix Bay, circa 1980 (Box 19)
  - 600,101 Little Dix Bay, 1980 (Box 19)
  - 600,102 Sandy Cay, circa 1980 (Box 19)
    Boats in marina; Caneel Bay Calypso; Sandy Cay from the water.
  - 600,103 Little Dix Bay, 1980 March (Box 19)
    Aerial and other views; Calypso.
  - 600,104 Little Dix Bay from North Island, 1980 May (Box 19)
    Photo by J. Fleming.
  - 600,105 Little Dix Bay and North Island (sunrise), 1980 May (Box 19)
  - 600,106 Caneel Bay, 1981 December (Box 19)
    LSR, MFR, views, vegetation.
  - 600,107 Caneel Bay, 1981 December (Box 19)
    MFR arriving at Caneel; Guests on beach; Cabin 7 terrace.
  - 600,108 Caneel Bay, 1981 December (Box 19)
    Santa; views; MFR, family.
  - 600,109 Caneel Bay, Sandy Cay, 1981 December (Box 19)
  - 600,110 Caneel Bay, 1981 December (Box 19)
  - 600,111 Sandy Cay; Little Dix Bay, 1981 December (Box 20)
  - 600,112 Little Dix Bay, 1981 December (Box 20)
  - 600,113 Little Dix Bay, 1981 December (Box 20)
  - 600,114 Little Dix Bay, 1981 December (Box 20)
    MFR, Evening Star, unidentified man (possibly Andrew Heiskell?).
  - 600,115 Caneel Bay, circa 1982 (Box 20)
    Harpur Woodward and LSR
  - 600,116 Caneel Bay, 1982 (Box 20)
  - 600,116.1 Caneel Bay, 1983 circa June (Box 20)
    Caneel Bay, MFR, unidentified guests, artwork in gift shop. Also includes two images from Vermont.
  - 600,116.2 Caneel Bay, 1983 circa June (Box 20)
    Includes images from Little Dix Bay. Steel drum band; MFR.
  - 600,116.3 Little Dix Bay, 1983 circa June (Box 20)
    Sandy Cay.
  - 600,117 Cinnamon Bay Campground, 1982 (Box 20)
  - 600,118 Little Dix Bay, circa 1982 (Box 20)
  - 600,119 Caneel Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
    Includes Sandy Cay and a few Dorado Beach images.
  - 600,120 Caneel Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
  - 600,121 Caneel Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
  - 600,122 Caneel Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
  - 600,123 Caneel Bay, 1983 December - 1984 January (Box 20)
  - 600,124 Little Dix Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
    MFR, LSR.
  - 600,125 Little Dix Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
  - 600,126 Little Dix Bay, Evening Star, 1984 January (Box 20)
  - 600,127 Little Dix Bay, 1984 (Box 20)
  - 600,128 Little Dix Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
    The Baths and Copper Mine ruins.
  - 600,129 Little Dix Bay, 1984 January (Box 20)
    Includes interior shots of living room.
  - 600,130 Sandy Cay, 1984 January (Box 20)
  - 600,131 British Virgin Islands, 1984 February (Box 20)
    House under construction; William and Mary Scranton.
  - 600,132 Little Dix Bay, 1980s (Box 20)
    LSR, MFR, Marion, sailing.
  - 600,133 Little Dix Bay, 1960s (Box 20)
    Undated Little Dix construction photos.
  - 600,134 St. John, 1985 February (Box 20)
    Caneel; Cruz Bay to Sandy Cay; Cruz Bay public toilets.
  - 600,135 Little Dix Bay, 1985 February (Box 20)
  - 600,136 Little Dix Bay, 1985 February (Box 20)
    LSR and MFR at Little Dix; Wildenstein house under construction?
  - 600,136.1 Little Dix Bay, Cruz Bay, 1985 February (Box 20)
    Harbor views; public toilets in Cruz Bay; paintings of Cruz Bay? and of woman cooking.
  - 600,137 Little Dix Bay, 1985 February (Box 20)
  - 600,138 Sandy Cay; Caneel Bay, 1985 February (Box 20)
  - 600,139 Hawaii, 1960s (Box 20)
    LSR, MFR, Millie Sample, and others.
  - 600,140 Hawaii- Mauna Lani, 1983 (Box 20)
    Opening ceremonies?
  - 600,141 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1968 September (Box 20)
    Opening of new wing.
  - 600,142 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, Undated (Box 20)
    View of beach from balcony. One image.
  - 600,143 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1960s (Box 20)
    Hotel construction and golf course; Ranch House, Kamuela; Bud O'Dell; Dale Hendrickson, golf manager; Jackie Pung, women's golf pro; couple identified only as "W" and "B."
  - 600,144 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, circa 1975 (Box 20)
    Photos of dedication ceremony and plaque in honor of Walter Collins, with Reverend Abraham Akaka; card from Akakas.
  - 600,145 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Construction, 1960s (Box 20)
  - 600,146 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Golf Tournament, 1964 (Box 21)
  - 600,147 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1962 August (Box 21)
    Prototype unit; undeveloped shore.
  - 600,148 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Model, 1964 March (Box 21)
  - 600,149 Unidentified, 1965 March (Box 21)
    LSR and Larry R. on fishing boat; whale spout.
  - 600,150 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel- Opening, 1965 July (Box 21)
  - 600,151 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1965 August (Box 21)
  - 600,152 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1966 July (Box 21)
    Views; installation of Akaji's "Happy Gathering Place" sculpture.
  - 600,153 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1971 February (Box 21)
    Display at Mauna Kea of bronze toys from an Indian Temple.
  - 600,154 Beach views - Hawaii?, 1972 June (Box 21)
    LSR, MFR.
  - 600,155 Unidentified Resort, 1972 August (Box 21)
  - 600,155.1 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1973 August (Box 21)
    Tennis court, beach.
  - 600,156 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel and Waikiki, 1974 December (Box 21)
  - 600,157 Hawaii, 1975 (Box 21)
    Sand pits, goats.
  - 600,158 Hawaii, 1975 (Box 21)
    Unidentified views.
  - 600,158.1 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1977 August (Box 21)
    Golf course, beach, views, horses.
  - 600,159 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1977 September (Box 21)
    Views from water.
  - 600,160 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1977 October (Box 21)
    Publicity and other views. Includes MFR golfing.
  - 600,161 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1977 October (Box 21)
  - 600,162 Hawaii, circa 1978 (Box 21)
    Mauna Kea views; Royal Hawaiian beach, Waikiki.
  - 600,162.1 Hawaii, 1978 February (Box 21)
    Unidentified construction; golf course; LSR and MFR.
  - 600,162.2 Hawaii, 1978 February (Box 21)
    Unidentified construction and condo development; golf course.
  - 600,162.3 Hawaii and 834 Fifth Ave, 1978 February (Box 21)
    Pool; snow on terrace at 834 Fifth Ave apartment.
  - 600,162.4 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1978 February (Box 21)
    Views, dedication ceremonies with Reverend Akaka. Includes photos of LSR with unidentified associates.
  - 600,162.5 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1978 February (Box 21)
  - 600,163 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel and Unidentified, 1978 February (Box 21)
    Mauna Kea views; drainage installation; unidentified building on waterway and pelicans on sand bar (possibly Florida).
  - 600,164 Hawaii, 1978 February (Box 21)
    Unidentified construction and condo development; LSR and MFR by golf course. (Same images as in 600,162.1 and 600,162.2.)
  - 600,165 Hawaii- Kahala Hilton, 1982 (Box 21)
    Flowers and Kahala Hilton.
  - 600,166 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1984 August (Box 21)
    Beach and hotel views.
  - 600,167 Hawaii, 1984 August-September (Box 21)
    Mauna Lani hotel and residences; Kahala Hilton; Outrigger Club lunch (Waikiki?),
  - 600,168 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1984 August 31 (Box 21)
    LSR and MFR by "Happy Gathering Place" sculpture and plaque; views; condos
  - 600,169 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1985 October (Box 21)
    LSR and Adi Kohler, manager of MKBH, by Samurai Horses.
  - 600,170 Little Dix Bay, 1985 December (Box 21)
    Views; LSR and MFR sailing. Envelope marked "trip to Sandy Cay."
  - 600,171 Caneel Bay, 1985 December (Box 23)
    Christmas, Waletzky family.
  - 600,172 Caneel Bay, 1985 December (Box 21)
    Caneel Bay, boats, tennis tournament.
  - 600,173 Caneel Bay, 1985 December (Box 21)
    Caneel Bay views and boats; Cruz Bay shop, construction.
  - 600,174 Sandy Cay, 1985 December (Box 21)
  - 600,175 Caneel Bay, 1985 December - 1987 (Box 22)
    Caneel Bay views, Sandy Cay, tennis tournament; LSR and MFR with Guy and Georgette Rutherfurd.
  - 600,176 (1) Little Dix Bay, 1985 December (Box 22)
    Boatyard, Andy Flax's new Bay restaurant, Sea Star, LSR and MFR in New Year's Eve hats.
  - 600,176 (2) Little Dix Bay, 1985 December (Box 22)
  - 600,177 Little Dix Bay and Caneel Bay, 1985 December (Box 22)
  - 600,177a Little Dix Bay and Caneel Bay, 1985 February (Box 22)
  - 600,178 Little Dix Bay, 1986 January (Box 22)
    Views; photo of framed photo of LSR receiving Order of the British Empire medallion.
  - 600,179 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 1985 October (Box 22)
    Flowers, views, MFR>
  - 600,180 Woodstock Sports Center, 1985 November 9 (Box 22)
    Construction.
  - 600,181 Caneel Bay; Little Dix Bay, 1987 (Box 22)
    Envelope includes several sets of negatives, with description.
  - 600,182 Dorado Beach Hotel, 1987 January (Box 22)
    LSR, MFR, Chi-Chi Rodriguez and wife, Leonard and Caroline Firestone
  - 600,183 Dorado Beach Hotel, 1987 circa January (Box 22)
    Views of hotel and grounds, MFR, LSR.
  - 600,184 St. Croix, Carambola Beach Resort, 1987 circa January (Box 22)
    LSR, MFR, Firestones, aerial views of Carambola resort.
  - 600,185 Mauna Kea Beach Hotel and Waikiki, 1987 circa February (Box 22)
    LSR and MFR, views, artwork; Waikiki; LSR with Year of the Rabbit paper.
  - 600,186 Woodstock Sports Center and Suicide Six Ski Area, 1986 December (Box 22)
  - 600,187 Caneel Bay; Little Dix Bay; Carambola, 1987 December - 1988 January (Box 22)
    Construction photos - Carambola
  - 600,188 Sandy Cay and Guana Island, 1987 December - 1988 January (Box 22)
  - 600,189 Caneel Bay, 1987 December (Box 23)
    Christmas. Waletzky family.
  - 600,190 Caneel Bay views; 834 Fifth Avenue, 1987 December - 1988 January (Box 22)
  - 600,191 (1) Mauna Kea Beach Hotel; San Francisco, 1988 February (Box 22)
  - 600,191 (2) Mauna Kea Beach Hotel; San Francisco, 1988 February (Box 22)
  - 600,192 (1) Hawaii, 1988 February (Box 22)
    Kahala Hilton, views of Diamond Head; floral arrangements, artwork, MFR.
  - 600,092 (2) Hawaii; 834 Fifth Avenue, 1988 February (Box 22)